{
  "type": "matching",
  "title": "Matching (1 point each)",
  "instructions": "Select the correct answer from the dropdown.",
  "points_per_question": 1,
  "prompts": [
    {
      "question": "Xbox's Killer App?",
      "answer": "Halo"
    },
    {
      "question": "What made loading much faster in the 9th generation of consoles?",
      "answer": "SSDs"
    },
    {
      "question": "Technology that superimposes a computer generated image or game on a user's view of the real world?",
      "answer": "Augmented Reality"
    },
    {
      "question": "What game first popularized the first person shooter genre?",
      "answer": "Doom"
    },
    {
      "question": "What 2009 game is widely considered the first Souls game?",
      "answer": "Demon's Souls"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who invented the predecessor to Monopoly in 1903, The Landlord's Game?",
      "answer": "Elizabeth Magie"
    },
    {
      "question": "A collection of API's that made it easy to develop, install, and run PC games?",
      "answer": "DirectX"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sega Genesis' Killer App?",
      "answer": "Sonic the Hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "What happened in the early 70s for electronic gaming?",
      "answer": "The Rise of Arcades"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first home video game system, which was invented by Ralph Bear in 1972?",
      "answer": "Magnavox Odyssey"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which video game contained a mod that popularized the Multiplayer Online Battle Arena (MOBA) genre?",
      "answer": "Warcraft 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What action-adventure survival did very poorly on initial release but slowly built up a base?",
      "answer": "No Man's Sky"
    },
    {
      "question": "Games prior to the 19th century were primarily ________ games",
      "answer": "multiplayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who pioneered the ability to play multiple games on a single console?",
      "answer": "Jerry Lawson"
    },
    {
      "question": "What sub-genre of game often required backtracking with new abilities to access new parts of previous areas",
      "answer": "Metroidvania"
    }
    
    
  ],
  "word_bank": [
    { "text": "Elizabeth Magie" },
    { "text": "Charles Darrow" },
    { "text": "Ralph Baer"},
    { "text": "Jerry Lawson"},
    { "text": "Nintendo Entertainment System" },
    { "text": "Magnavox Odyssey" },
    { "text": "Pong" },
    { "text": "Pac-Man" },
    { "text": "Tennis for Two" },
    { "text": "Spacewar" },
    { "text": "The Rise of Arcades" },
    { "text": "The Crash and Recovery of the Game Industry" },
    { "text": "SSDs" },
    { "text": "CPUs" },
    { "text": "Halo" },
    { "text": "Call of Duty" },
    { "text": "Doom" },
    { "text": "DirectX"},
    { "text": "Visual Studio"},
    { "text": "Donkey Kong" },
    { "text": "Augmented Reality" },
    { "text": "Virtual Reality" },
    { "text": "Sonic the Hedgehog" },
    { "text": "The Legend of Zelda" },
    { "text": "Super Mario Bros." },
    { "text": "Demon's Souls"},
    { "text": "Dark Souls" },
    { "text": "Defense of the Ancients (DOTA)"},
    { "text": "Warcraft 3"},
    { "text": "No Man's Sky"},
    { "text": "The Outer Worlds"},
    { "text": "Multi-Player"},
    { "text": "Single-Player"},
    { "text": "Metroidvania"},
    { "text": "Roguelike"}
    
  ]
}
